character = Deck.create(topic: "Movies by Main Character")

jack = character.cards.create(question: "What movie is Jack Dawson from?", answer: "Titanic")
jack2 = character.cards.create(question: "What movie is Jack Skellington from?", answer: "The Nightmare before Christmas")
dori = character.cards.create(question: "What movie is Dori from?", answer: "Finding Nemo")
elsa = character.cards.create(question: "What movie is Elsa and Anna from?", answer: "Frozen")
jason = character.cards.create(question: "What movie is Jason Voorhees from?", answer: "Friday the 13th")
pennywise = character.cards.create(question: "What movie is Pennywise from?", answer: "It")
regina = character.cards.create(question: "What movie is Regina George from?", answer: "Mean Girls")
maximus = character.cards.create(question: "What movie is Maximus from?", answer: "Gladiator")
hon = character.cards.create(question: "What movie is Hon Solo from?", answer: "Star Wars")
neo = character.cards.create(question: "What movie is Neo from?", answer: "The Matrix")
